http://www.mainfilter.com/privacy-policy.aspx

Cross Reference
Follow us:
Become a DistributorDistributor Login
Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site.
Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information.
By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy.
These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply
to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged
to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you
understand how any personal information you provide will be used.
Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.
Collection of Information
We collect personally identifiable information such as names, postal addresses,
and email addresses, etc, when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information
you provide is used to fulfill your specific request. This information is only used
to fulfill your specific request unless you give us permission to use it in another
manner, for example, to add you to one of our mailing lists.
Cookie/Tracking Technology
The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie
and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and
operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how
visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal
information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology; however,
if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied
to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.
Distribution of Information
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention
or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect
against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating
fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.
Commitment to Data Security
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents, and
contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this
information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.
Privacy Contact Information
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:
By Phone: 800-465-MAIN(6246)
By Email: information@mainfilter.com
We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
One of the largest hydraulic cross references available!
Start searching!
